# Olisaeloka, Ejike-Nweze

(431) 999-2488 | nwezeolisa@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Olisaeloka Ejike-Nweze | GitHub: olisanweze

Winnipeg, Manitoba

#### \_

**PROFILE** 

A diligent Junior Full-stack Software Development student, with experience working with front-end technologies like HTML, CSS, React, Git, JavaScript, and back-end technologies like C#. Proven expertise working effectively with teams using problem-solving and listening skills.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

• JavaScript, WordPress, Figma, UI, UX, C#, .NET, SSMS, React, Git, HTML, and CSS.

## **EDUCATION**

# Software Developer, Manitoba Institute of Trades and Technology

January 2024 - December 2024

Winnipeg, Manitoba

## **Electrical/Electronic Engineering, Bells University of Technology**

**September 2014 – June 2019** 

Ota, Ogun State, Nigeria CGPA 4.10/5.00

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Aryval October 2024 - December 2024

Junior Full Stack Developer (Student Intern)

Designing and implementing the company website using Figma, WordPress, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Git.

Ditchfield Soils Ltd. April 2024 - Present

Retail Counter Associate

• Processing customer orders, product enquiries and handling cash transactions.

## Escher Silverman Global

March 2023 - December 2023

Junior Engineer/IT Admin

- Updating company website and maintaining employee email accounts using cPanel.
- Preparing relevant project documents.

#### Mar & Mor Engineering Services Ltd.

November 2020 - June 2021

Junior Engineer Intern

### **EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

### Contestant, Manitoba Institute of Trades and Technology ICT Hackathon

May 2024

Participated and placed 3<sup>rd</sup> overall in the MITT (Manitoba Institute of Trades and Technology) ICT Hackathon

#### **AWARDS**

Manitoba Institute of Trades and Technology International Student Scholarship Award

June 2024

#### **PROJECTS**

## Car Rental Website using HTML and CSS

Link to website: https://olisanweze.github.io/car-rental/

Demonstrated the use of HTML and CSS by building an interactive webpage for a car rental website.

## **Typing Game using JavaScript**

Link to website: https://olisanweze.github.io/typepacer/

This is a typing game that was developed using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. This game stores users high scores in the local storage.

## **GitHub Finder Website using React**

Link to website: https://github-finder-olisanweze.netlify.app/

This project is built using React. This project uses the GitHub API to fetch GitHub user data as requested.